

## Arman Ajabkhani

SENIOR JAVA DEVELOPER - BACK END

#### **PROFILE**

Gender: Male Nationality: Iranian Birth Date: 8/25/1983

A software engineer with more than 10 years experience in software developing with Several roles including developer, designer, team lead in various projects.

Communicative, high interaction with team-mates, responsibility and perseverance, and issue solving. Motivated and intrested in learning new concepts, technical challanges and distributed systems and also improving the Software Quality(functional or non-functional)

## **EDUCATION**

**Bachelor of Science** from Sheikh Bahaee Isfahan University in Software Engineering from September 2000 to September 2006.

#### **LANGUAGES**

**English** 

Persian

#### **CONTACT**

Email: arm.khani@gmail.com Mobile: +98 912 8589 456

LinkedIn: Arman Ajabkhani's profile

Github: Arman Ajabkhani's profile

Address: No. 23, Parastoo2 Alley, Kaj St.,

Taherkhani St., Tehran, Iran

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

### SNAPP(Largest smart transportation system in Iran)

## Senior Java Developer

July 2019 - Present

Senior java developer in Fintech team:

- Designing and implementing new generation Financial management services for users and drivers.
- Providing services for more than 2 million users.
- Developing services with SpringBoot, Spring Cloud, MySql, OpenShift and Redis.
- Responsible for designing and development of Payment and Wallet Management Services.

#### Sava Arman Kish(a crypto-currencies Exchange start-up)

## Senior Java Developer

Nov 2018 - Jul 2019

Senior java developer in the Exchange back-end team:

- Developing reactive services using RxJava and Vert.x and Swagger.
- Responsible for designing, development and maintaining CRM and notification services.
- Designing and implementing features and fixing bug in several micro-services.

## TOSAN(Payment and Banking solution provider)

#### Senior Java Developer /Team Lead

Nov 2011 -Nov 2018

Team lead in Channel Manager team:

- Mentoring, coaching, training and planning tasks for the team members.
- Analysis, Design, Development, Deployment & Maintenance several applications & micro-services.
- Designing and developing some complicated features in open banking API.

Senior java developer in Channel Manager Team:

- Developing functionalities for tracking and authentication and authorization.
- Developing and maintaining Exchange and Corporate Banking subsystems.
- Providing serveral financial and payment services for front-end teams.
- Developing and implementing RMI and Web Services (REST / SOAP JAX-WS).
- Implementing many feature in Persistence layer using JPA/Hibernate

#### Elm o Sanat

#### C#/ASP.NET Developer

Sep 2010 -Oct 2011

- Implementing several new features and maintain in the School product.
- Implementing features in a custom report generator.
- Implementing virtual replication on SQL Server with use web service.

### Netbina (Online advertising solution provider)

## Junior C#/ASP.NET Developer

Oct 2006 -Mar 2009

- Implementing several functionalities for the advertising products.
- Developing a several feature in Blog Service with C# and ASP.NET.



# Arman Ajabkhani SENIOR JAVA DEVELOPER - BACK END

## PROGRAMMING SKILLS

Spring
Spring Boot
Spring MVC
Spring Security
Spring Cloud
Spring Batch
Spring Data / JPA/ Hibernate
Spring AOP / aspectj
Vert.x / RxJava
Redis / Redisson
Oracle
MySQL / SQL Server
Gradle / Maven
Swagger UI/ Codegen
Git / Subversion / TFS
ActiveMQ/ Rabbit MQ
Apache Tomcat
OAuth / JWT
JUnit / TestNg / Mockito
C#
LATEX .